<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<list>
  <sentences>
    <s path="[OANC]/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="4538" end="4541" sStart="4506" offset="32" sid="r7.1.use.v.0327" wn="1" wnkey="use%2:34:01::" text="Electrosurgical devices use variable waveform shape and duty cycle duration to achieve fulguration, cutting, or desiccation [ 15 16 ] . In general the application of energy with electrosurgical devices is intense for an extremely short period of time (several seconds)." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="3562" end="3573" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="transfer%2:40:01::" text="At microwave frequencies, energy is primarily &lt;b&gt;transferred&lt;/b&gt; to tissue via capacitive coupling (field heating) which causes vibration of particles in tissues, resulting in tissue heating." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="3791" end="3802" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="transfer%2:40:01::" text="At frequencies used by radiofrequency ablation devices, energy is &lt;b&gt;transferred&lt;/b&gt; primarily by conductive (ohmic) heating, where current is generated through the movement of charge from the ablation probe to the electrical ground plate via the path of least resistance." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="4325" end="4333" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="7" wnkey="transfer%2:35:00::" text="In electrosurgical devices, high bursts of energy are used for short periods of time to achieve cutting and coagulative effects on tissues [ 12 13 14 ] . Electrosurgical devices and radiofrequency ablation probes both operate within the same frequency range and &lt;b&gt;transfer&lt;/b&gt; energy in similar ways, but differ in the shape of stimulation waveforms." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="10144" end="10152" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="4 7" wnkey="null" text="Heat &lt;b&gt;transfer&lt;/b&gt; in tissue is governed by the heat conduction equation" />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/technical/biomed/1475-925X-2-12.anc" start="5604" end="5608" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="4" wnkey="date%1:28:02::" text="There are no known studies to &lt;b&gt;date&lt;/b&gt; that specifically study the effects of temperature dependent electrical properties on the dosimetric and heat transfer profiles surrounding ablation probes [ 19 20 ] . Perhaps the greatest reason for assuming constant electrical properties is the enormous computational advantage of being able to separate the electromagnetic and heat transfer problems." />
  </sentences>
</list>