<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<list>
  <sentences>
    <s path="file:/c:/OANC/data/written_1/journal/slate/43/ArticleIP_3368.anc" start="140" end="144" sStart="-1" offset="0" sid="null" wn="6" wnkey="land%1:26:00::" annotator="cgozo" text="Inventing a holy &lt;b&gt;land&lt;/b&gt;,who would have settled for theseneutral hills bare except for scrub and sage,a sky unclouded as impenetrable,now and then the timeless Bedouin tent--which would explain, along that ridge,a straggling flock of goatswith stretched-out, walking shadows?" />
    <s path="[OANC]/data/written_1/journal/slate/43/ArticleIP_3368.anc" start="1621" end="1625" sStart="null" offset="305" sid="r11.dark.j.0248" wn="1" wnkey="dark%3:00:01::" annotator="anfahmy" text="Remember the hands, calloused and sunburned,of the Quumran scribes, seated at a cave's mouth,negotiating light that dawn brought backwith the promise of deliverance.Shadow and light, black fireon white fire, the unswerving word,conferring a sacred indifferenceto an urban, merely visual appeal.The caves, dark sockets in a cliff wall,return no one's gaze today,even if they once did seea mountain range of crumpled felt,castiron eagles fixed on approaching spears,and a southbound Jordan feeding the samefluid body, ever moremineral, ever heavier with salt." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_1/journal/slate/43/ArticleIP_3368.anc" start="621" end="626" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="7" wnkey="color%1:07:01::" annotator="brubin" text="Yet nothingabout the frontier's fenced compoundssuggests the traveller en route elsewhereshould stop--even if stepping on the gascan't do much toward cancelling those pictures,the &lt;b&gt;color&lt;/b&gt; of pain, a visual undersong ...Once coppergreen expanses of waterslide into view, though, no one could failto sense the difference in beingbelow sea level--air heavyin the ear, oxygen-rich, cool, dry,scented with desert, and holy enough.A hand dipped in water pondersthe viscous feel of minerals in solution,and little tumuli of salts and carbonatesbuild a submarine city sprawlingfor miles under the hammered-metal surface.On a shore hazed with distance, neat rowsof &lt;b&gt;date&lt;/b&gt; palms identify themselveswith a green herringbone frond and ripen foodstuffs for, say, the heavenly banquet.Ritual ablution even so has coatedyour skin with a pale silt glove;and sea and desert are one." />
  </sentences>
</list>