<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<list>
  <sentences>
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/OANC/data/written_1/journal/verbatim/VOL15_3.anc" start="69776" end="69782" sStart="-1" offset="0" sid="null" wn="1" wnkey="write%2:36:00::" annotator="veweser" text="Those familiar with Safire's editorial style, reflected in his political columns on the editorial pages of The N. Y. Times , may agree with me in the contention that when he &lt;b&gt;writes&lt;/b&gt; about language he seems to be &lt;b&gt;writing&lt;/b&gt; on his day off: I cannot put my finger on why, but ÒOn LanguageÓ always strikes me as an excruciating effort to be cute." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/OANC/data/written_1/journal/verbatim/VOL15_3.anc" start="47503" end="47510" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2147483645" wnkey="null" annotator="veweser" text="Even the remnants we have from early languages that had a &lt;b&gt;writing&lt;/b&gt; system are relatively sparse: Classical Latin and &lt;b&gt;Greek&lt;/b&gt;, Hebrew, and a few other languages are better documented than others; but for most all we have to go on are a handful of tablets here, a few inscriptions there, barely enough in many cases to allow us to identify the language, let alone draw any conclusions regarding its structure or meaning." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/OANC/data/written_1/journal/verbatim/VOL15_3.anc" start="74745" end="74752" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="write%2:32:00::" annotator="tofox" text="While I acknowledge that it is not easy to know how to sort out the many topics to be covered in a usage book, most reasonable writers have taken a stab at &lt;b&gt;writing&lt;/b&gt; an entry under a heading that seems a likely place to look, then have provided a detailed index." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/OANC/data/written_1/journal/verbatim/VOL15_3.anc" start="71779" end="71786" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2147483645" wnkey="null" annotator="tofox" text="&lt;b&gt;Writing&lt;/b&gt; containing such labored figures makes for hard reading." />
  </sentences>
</list>