<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<list>
  <sentences>
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="720" end="725" sStart="-1" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2147483647" wnkey="null" text="For instance Fabiola Cabeza de Baca, Cleofas Jaramillo, and Nina Otero all &lt;b&gt;wrote&lt;/b&gt; about the weddings of northern New Mexico." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="720" end="725" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2147483647" wnkey="null" text="For instance Fabiola Cabeza de Baca, Cleofas Jaramillo, and Nina Otero all &lt;b&gt;wrote&lt;/b&gt; about the weddings of northern New Mexico." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="6185" end="6192" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="write%2:32:00::" text="Almost all publications on Chicanos and Mexicanos up to that date had been &lt;b&gt;written&lt;/b&gt; by Anglo American sociologists or anthropologists, and the few published Hispano scholars, such as Aurelio Espinosa and Arthur Campa, were only known within a narrow circle of folklore specialists." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="720" end="725" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="write%2:32:00::" text="For instance Fabiola Cabeza de Baca, Cleofas Jaramillo, and Nina Otero all &lt;b&gt;wrote&lt;/b&gt; about the weddings of northern New Mexico." />
    <s path="file:/D:/Corpora/oanc/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="614" end="621" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2147483647" wnkey="null" text="The southwestern region with the most researched and documented wedding customs is New Mexico, because the descendents of the early Hispanos have been conscious of describing and &lt;b&gt;writing&lt;/b&gt; down their traditions." />
    <s path="file:/c:/OANC/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="4646" end="4650" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="work%1:06:00::" text="It was in this &lt;b&gt;work&lt;/b&gt; that Paredes proposed his theory of the production of Chicano folklore, and especially the border ballad, as a result of a process of border conflict generated by the invasion of Anglo culture and values into the Texas region in the early nineteenth century." />
    <s path="file:/c:/OANC/data/written_2/non-fiction/OUP/Castro/chW.anc" start="4033" end="4038" sStart="null" offset="0" sid="null" wn="2" wnkey="work%1:06:00::" text="With His Pistol in His Hand: A Border Ballad and Its Hero, published in 1958 by the University of Texas Press, is not only one of the most important academic &lt;b&gt;works&lt;/b&gt; on the history of the Chicano, but it is also respected as major scholarship in the field of folklore studies, and specifically on the genre of the ballad." />
  </sentences>
</list>